Loc Ngo

Vietnam

danielngo1998@gmail.com

+84393238017

linkedin.com/in/loc-ngo-532902195

Summary

I am a software engineer with more than two years of experience in software development. I possess a robust foundation in backend development utilizing Java and Springboot framework. However, I am open to exploring and contributing to various domains within the field of software engineering.

I consistently approach my work with a can-do attitude and demonstrate a strong motivation to enhance my skills and knowledge to effectively solve complex problems.

Experience



Software Engineer

mesoneer

Aug 2022 - Present (1 year 8 months)

- Work as a cross-functional team member for developing and maintaining applications in the fintech domain.
- Analyzing and verifying the requirements.
- Estimating and finding the solutions for solving the problems.
- Collaborate with the team as well as work independently.
- Learning and applying technologies and tools for solving technical problems.

Techstack: Springboot, Kustomize, Jenkins, oauth2-proxy, Keycloak, Spring Data JPA, Flyway, Testcontainer, Angular.

Software Engineer

DXC Technology

Nov 2019 - Apr 2020 (6 months)

Developing web applications using Java stack

Techstack: Java Core, HTML, CSS.



🥏 Engineer Intern

ZAMO

Apr 2019 - Jul 2019 (4 months)

Developing backend API for the dental clinic project

Learning about software development

Techstack: Springboot, Liqibase, Postgresql.

Education

VEF Academy

Java Enterprise

Nov 2021 - Dec 2022

Joined Java Enterprise Applications class at VEF academy. Learned so much about microservices and trending technologies at there. I also developed crawler system which applied some microservices architecture patterns.



Ton Duc Thang University

Computer Science

Skills

Java • Object-Oriented Programming (OOP) • Spring Framework • Spring Boot • JavaScript • SQL • JPA • docker • Jenkins